<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>code on </title>
    <link>https://sivula.io/tags/code/</link>
    <description>Recent content in code on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://sivula.io/tags/code/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Jamstack has matured</title>
      <link>https://sivula.io/posts/jamstack-has-matured/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sivula.io/posts/jamstack-has-matured/</guid>
      <description>In the beginning Jamstack was fun. The main SSG was Jekyll, which was simple and open-source. It was not only free to use, but also free to host (on Github). Jamstack websites were blazing fast and scored high in Google Lighthouse. There were plenty of free CMS options to choose from. The Jamstack looked very promising! But times have changed&amp;hellip;&#xA;Jekyll is dead Sure&amp;hellip; you can still use Jekyll. But Jekyll lost its most important developer and Github decided to freeze their Jekyll version.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code is poetry</title>
      <link>https://sivula.io/posts/code-is-poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sivula.io/posts/code-is-poetry/</guid>
      <description>I found the words &amp;lsquo;code is poetry&amp;rsquo; in the footer of the new Wordpress frontpage, that has been launched recently. I fully agree that code is poetry! I love to read and write beautiful and concise code.&#xA;In a few days I will even be joining CloudCannon on their Youtube show &amp;lsquo;Static Feedback&amp;rsquo; to talk about Artisanal Web Development. This is my hand-crafted take on building sites with absolute knowledge about every line of code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has WebP landed yet?</title>
      <link>https://sivula.io/posts/has-webp-landed-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://sivula.io/posts/has-webp-landed-yet/</guid>
      <description>Those who know me, know I care about DX just as much as UX. I will not use a feature that requires prefixes, polyfills or other wizardry. I can wait for a feature to land in your browser. The question I asked myself today (from this perspective) was: Has WebP landed yet?&#xA;Although it is supported in almost any browser, it is not fully supported in Safari on macOS. Safari supports WebP, but it is not working on macOS versions below Big Sur (macOS 11).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
